Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 568 records 1947-2011 IBT0039
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Local 568 records
1947-2011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0039
15.75 Linear Feet
This series contains material produced by IBT Local 568 and related unions dating from 1947-2011. Included are contracts, agreements, company files, correspondence, meeting minutes, newsletters, dues ledgers, handbooks and a variety of other materials related to the union's operation and organizing activities.
Scope and Contents
This series contains material produced by IBT Local 568 and related unions dating from 1947-2011. Included are contracts, agreements, company files, correspondence, meeting minutes, newsletters, dues ledgers, handbooks and a variety of other materials related to the union's operation and organizing activities. Also of note are materials related to The Real Teamsters Caucus, Teamsters for a Democratic Union, and the Local 568 "Justice for Hoffa" Committee.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2012 [2012.0]
Arrangement
Collection: Organized into two series: Contracts and Agreements and General files.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Labor and laboring classes; Labor unions; Labor; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- Louisiana -- History -- 20th century
- Contracts and Agreements, 1949-2011; Series 1; 9 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  This series is organized into two subseries, Subseries 1: Published Agreements and Subseries 2: Negotiation and Agreements.
  - Published Agreements, 1949-2011; Series 1 Subseries 1; 5 Linear Feet
    This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    Scope and Contents
    This subseries contains published, pamphlet-style labor contracts and agreements dating from 1949-2011. Included are National Master Freight agreements and regional supplements, IBT Local 568 agreements, regional and state-wide agreements, and other miscellaneous IBT local union agreements.
    - Agreements, 1949-1955; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Agreements, 1955-1958; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Agreements, 1958-1961; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 1961-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Agreements, 1962-1964; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Agreements, 1964-1966; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Agreements, 1967; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Agreements, 1967-1969; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Agreements, 1970; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 1970; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Agreements, 1970-1972; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Agreements, 1973; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Agreements, 1973; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Agreements, 1973-1974; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Agreements, 1974-1976; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 1976-1977; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Agreements, 1977-1979; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Agreements, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Agreements, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Agreements, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Agreements, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Agreements, 1980-1981; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Agreements, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Agreements, 1981-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Agreements, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Agreements, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Agreements, 1983-1984; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Agreements, 1984-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Agreements, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Agreements, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Agreements, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Agreements, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Agreements, 1985-1986; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Agreements, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Agreements, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Agreements, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Agreements, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Agreements, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Agreements, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Agreements, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Agreements, 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Agreements, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Agreements, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Agreements, 1997-1998; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Agreements, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Agreements, 1999-2002; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Agreements, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Agreements, 2008-2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Negotiation and Agreements, 1970-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2; 4 Linear Feet
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically.
    This subseries contains files of IBT Local 568 from 1970-1995 arranged by company or type. In addition to Local 568 the subseries also contains agreements with IBT Locals 391 and 891, as well as various AFL local unions. Included are many original signed labor agreements, as well as related negotiation materials, meeting minutes and correspondence. Also of note are National Master Freight Agreements and Southern Conference Area Agreements.
    - Al Johnson Construction, 1983 January 24; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - American Bakeries Company, 1983 December 22; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - American Linen Company, 1979-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Amoco Oil Company, 1980 March 15; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Associated General Contractors of America [1/2], 1972-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Associated General Contractors of America [2/2], 1982-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Auto Convoy Company, 1982-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Big State Freight Lines, Inc., 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Borden, Inc., 1984 June 1; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Braswell Motor Freight, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Cadillac Wire and Cable Company, 1985 January; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Colton Contractors, Inc., 1983 June 2; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Continental Baking Company, 1987 June 6-12; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Cotton Brothers Baking Company [1/2], 1978-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Cotton Brothers Baking Company [2/2], 1983-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Curtis Parker Oil Company, 1978 October 24; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - F & W Express, Inc., 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - The Florsheim Company, 1983 June 3; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Foremost Dairies, Inc., 1982-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Frost Whited Company, 1973-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Fruehauf Corporation, 1978-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - General Presidents' Project Maintenance Agreement, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Highway and Heavy Construction Agreements, 1977-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - IBT Construction Agreements, 1980s; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Independent Ice and Cold Storage Company, 1977 April 27; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Interstate Brands Corporation, 1990-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - ITT Continental Baking Company, 1978-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - J.A. Jones Construction Company, 1981 January 14; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Lebus Manufacturing, Inc. [1/3], 1981-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lebus Manufacturing, Inc. [2/3], 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Lebus Manufacturing, Inc. [3/3], 1990-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Linen Services Companies, 1970 December 1; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - M.B. Fowlder Construction Company, 1984 February 28; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Malone and Hyde, Inc., 1982 April 26; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Master Rail-Truck Freight Agreement for the Southwest Area, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - McDowell Tire Company, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Midwest Farms, 1981-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Montgomery Ward and Company [1/2], 1980-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Montgomery Ward and Company [2/2], 1982-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Morton Thiokol, Inc. [1/2], 1982-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Morton Thiokol, Inc. [2/2], 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Murphy Bonded Warehouse, Inc., 1979-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Nabisco, Inc. [1/2], 1971-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Nabisco, Inc. [2/2], 1983-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - National Linen Service, 1985-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - National Master Automobile Transporters Agreements, 1982-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - National Master Freight Agreements, 1970-1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - National Master Freight Agreements: Southern Conference Supplements, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - National Pipe Line Agreement, 1981 March 4; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Pal-Tex Transport Company, 1973-1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Piggly Wiggly Operators Warehouse, Inc., 1980-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Pullman Incorporated, 1978 March 5; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - R.A. Corbett Transport, Inc., 1972-1978; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - SCA Services of Louisiana, Inc., 1977-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Shreveport Budweiser Distributors, Inc., 1984-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Shreveport Industrial Uniform and Louisiana Shop Towel [1/2], 1978 December 12; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Shreveport Industrial Uniform and Louisiana Shop Towel [2/2], 1981-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Shreveport-Bossier Cleaners and Laundries Association, Inc., 1981-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Southern Conference Area Agreements [1/2], 1972-1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Southern Conference Area Agreements [2/2], 1992-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Steve D. Thompson Trucking Company, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Sunshine Biscuits, Inc., 1973 December 4; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Texas Oklahoma Express, 1984 February 17; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Thompson-Hayward Chemical Company, 1975-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Thorton's Drivers Service, Inc., 1977 January 3; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - T.I.M.E. DC, Inc., 1982-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - TNT Bestway, Inc., 1991 February 7; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Town of Lake Providence, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Vine Tire Service, Inc., 1979 May 30; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Weyerhaeuser Company, 1978-1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Wheeling Pipe Line, Inc., 1977-1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Witco Chemical Corporation, 1972-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Wolf Baking Company, 1975-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Agreements, 1972-1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- General Files, 1947-2000; Series 2; 6.75 Linear Feet
  This series is arranged alphabetically by file title.
  This series contains material produced by IBT Local 568 and related unions dating from 1947-2000. Included are company files, correspondence, meeting minutes, newsletters, dues ledgers, handbooks and a variety of other materials related to the union's operation and organizing activities. Also of note are materials related to The Real Teamsters Caucus, Teamsters for a Democratic Union, and the Local 568 "Justice for Hoffa" Committee.
  - ABF Freight System, Inc. [1/2], 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - ABF Freight System, Inc. [2/2], 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Alliance for Labor Action Founding Conference Proceedings, 1969; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Articles and Publications, 1985-1995; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Associated General Contractors of America Construction News Letter, 1982-1983; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Braswell Motor Freight Lines, 1961-1971; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Braswell Motor Freight Lines Back Pay, 1977; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Braswell Motor Freight Lines Bankruptcy, 1977; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Central States Southeast and Southwest Areas Health and Welfare Fund, 1968-1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Continental Baking Company, 1984-1990; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: IBT [1/2], 1974-1986; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: IBT [2/2], 1982-1987; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Local 568, 1969-1987; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Political, 1976-1977; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Southern Conference of Teamsters, 1974-1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Democratic, Republican, Independent, Voter Education (DRIVE), 1964; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Dues Ledgers [1/4], 1952-1974; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Dues Ledgers [2/4], 1967-1977; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Dues Ledgers [3/4], 1967-1977; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Dues Ledgers [4/4], 1968-1977; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - F & W Express, Inc., 1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Fine Truck Line, 1979-1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Frito-Lay, Inc., 1983; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Fruehauf Corporation, 1985; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - General Office File, 1982-1983; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Handbooks and Manuals [1/6], 1957-1970; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Handbooks and Manuals [2/6], 1965-1970; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Handbooks and Manuals [3/6], 1970s; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Handbooks and Manuals [4/6], 1970-1972; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Handbooks and Manuals [5/6], 1975-1984; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Handbooks and Manuals [6/6], 1980-1989; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Hazardous Materials Transportation Awareness Training, 1995; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - IBT Constitutions, 1961-1966; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - IBT Jurisdictional Agreements and Decisions [1/4], undated; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - IBT Jurisdictional Agreements and Decisions [1/4], undated; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - IBT Jurisdictional Agreements and Decisions [2/4], undated; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - IBT Jurisdictional Agreements and Decisions [3/4], undated; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - IBT Jurisdictional Agreements and Decisions [4/4], undated; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - IBT No Raid Mutual Aid Pacts, 1975-1984; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - IBT Rituals, undated; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - IBT Rosters [1/2], 1977-1981; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - IBT Rosters [2/2], 1994-2000; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Insurance, Health, and Welfare Information, 1959-1985; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - "The International Teamster" Magazine, 1968 May - 1969 September; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - "The International Teamster" Magazine, 1969 October - 1971 June; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - "The International Teamster" Magazine, 1971 July - 1972 May; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - "The International Teamster" Magazine, 1972 June - 1973 May; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - "The International Teamster" Magazine, 1973 September - 1974 June; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - "The International Teamster" Magazine, 1974 July - 1975 September; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - "The International Teamster" Magazine, 1975 October - 1976 October; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - "The International Teamster" Magazine, 1976 December - 1986 February; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - "The International Teamster" Magazine, 1986 April - 1997 January; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Job Stewards Training Seminar, 1983; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Jones Truck Lines, Inc., 1982; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - "Justice for Hoffa" Committee, 1964; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Local 19 By-Laws, 1972; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Local 28 Newsletter, 1984; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Local 568 By-Laws, 1970; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Local 568 Flyers, undated; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Local 568 Newsletter, 1978-1990; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Local 767 By-Laws, 1990; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - McLean Trucking Company, undated; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes: Central-Southern Joint Arbitration Committee, 1982; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes: Executive Board, 1976-1977; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes: Executive Board, 1977; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Minutes: Executive Board, 1978; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Minutes: Executive Board, 1979; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Meeting Minutes: General Membership, 1976; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Meeting Minutes: General Membership, 1977; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Meeting Minutes: General Membership, 1978; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes: General Membership, 1979; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes: National Automobile Transporters, 1982; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes: Southern Conference, 1982; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Morrison-Knudsen Company, Inc., 1990; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1977-1984; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Overnite Transportation Company, 1981; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Pamphlets [1/2], 1965-1981; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Pamphlets [2/2], 1986-1997; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - The Real Teamsters Caucus, 1994; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Reports, 1982-1996; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Ryder/P.I.E. Nationwide, Incorporated, 1983; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Southern Conference of Teamsters, 1968-1975; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Southern Conference of Teamsters By-Laws, 1957-1989; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Spector Red Ball, Inc., 1982; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Steve D. Thompson Trucking, Inc., undated; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Teamsters Convention Delegate Lists, 1986-1991; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Teamsters Convention Proceedings, 1971; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Teamsters for a Democratic Union Handbook [1/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters for a Democratic Union Handbook [2/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters for a Democratic Union Handbook [3/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Hazardous Waste Worker Training Program [1/3], 1992; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Hazardous Waste Worker Training Program [2/3], 1992; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Teamsters Hazardous Waste Worker Training Program [3/3], 1992; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Teamsters Joint Council 80, 1981-1985; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Teamsters "Legislative Report" Newsletter, 1983; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters National Freight Industry Negotiating Committee, 1975-1981; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters News Releases, 1987-1988; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Privilege Benefits Guide, 1996; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Texas Conference of Teamsters, 1979-1983; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Town of Lake Providence, 1982; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Uniform Substance Abuse Policy, undated; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Union Labor Manual, Volume 2, 1947; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - "Union Labor Report" Newsletter, 1983; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Union Representation Authorization Forms, undated; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Department of Transporation Motor Carrier Safety Regulations, undated; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Yellow Freight System, Inc. [1/2], 1977; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Yellow Freight System, Inc. [2/2], 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959-1993; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)